I start to learn how to cook. What's the
Mbappe special? Uh for example, nothing.
For the moment, nothing, but I I try to
be better.
>> [music]
>> Hi guys. It's Kylian Mbappe and I'm here
on my Vanity Fair cover shoot. [music]
What do you know now about being a pro
athlete that you wish someone had told
you when you were 16? Oh, I would tell
him like to dream big, to stay humble,
and to trust the process because it's a
long journey to be an athlete. When I
was 16, I just wanted to be a football
player, to play the best game, to play
in the best teams, to be happy also on
the pitch, to don't lose my passion for
the game. Also to be happy outside
football because that's help you to have
a wonderful career, to be happy with
your family, with your loved ones. It's
always important. Do you have
friendships that have nothing to do with
football? Yeah, of course. Of course. I
have friends that I met them outside
football. I have friends that I met them
before I was football player. I think
it's important also to keep a balance
because football it's
just
a big thing in my life, but there is not
only football in life. So it's good to
open my mind to other things and to
explore everything I can explore. I try
to do normal things first because there
is nothing normal in the world in the
football. I have one friend like he
don't care about football. So all the
time we start talking about football for
for him it's so boring. So he say, "You
have nothing else in your life than
football."
But it's it's it's my friends.
Kylian, what's something people would be
surprised to hear that you do in your
spare time?
Oh, I think they will be surprised
to know that sometimes in my day off I
love to do nothing and stay home because
everybody think our life is so exciting.
We do everywhere and thing, but
sometimes we just love to chill at home
and do nothing like everybody. And I
know because sometimes one day was a
friend of me who bring a friend to my
house and he was surprised that I was
like doing nothing. He was thinking that
everybody was like super fast, super
chill. I say, "No, no, no. It's just
Sunday. I want to stay home." I start to
learn how to cook. What's the Mbappe
special? Uh for example, nothing. Uh for
the moment, nothing. But I I try to be
better. But it's something that I want
to improve, you know? When I'm home, I
think when you can cook something good
at home for someone or for yourself,
it's it's something good. What was the
first thing that genuinely surprised you
about Madrid? Oh, a little bit
everything because I have to be honest
when I I arrive in Madrid,
I absolutely no idea about the city.
Nothing. But I was surprised about the
culture, about the people, about the way
they are welcoming, about the way they
want to help all the time, but also the
food. It's the good food. It's difficult
to match with French food, but they they
try to do it. It's not It's not bad.
And and also the weather the weather is
so nice. It's peaceful to to be in a
place like this and and I really enjoy
my time in Madrid. Uh we have fans all
around the world. Uh of course in
Madrid, even more. Uh but of course it's
the greatest club in the world and the
most famous club. Uh we have love We
receive love from everywhere. Even now
that I come with national team
uh for games and there is many Madrid
fans. Yesterday at the stadium was the
same. It's It's the big club in the
world, so it's such a blessing to be to
be part of this club and this project.
The thing that surprised me the most
when I used to arrive and they eat so
late. In France, we are like at 9:00 is
breakfast, at 12:00 is the lunch, at
8:00 is dinner. Then it's like chill.
Everything is chill. Uh they always say
when you say something, they say
"Tranquilo." It's okay. They take it
easy, you know? They let the things come
to to them and it's really funny because
they have no pressure in everything.
They have no pressure and and it's
something that I learned from from
Spanish people like they
they are like easy. Come on, let's go
outside.
I hope it is not that cold outside.
>> [music]
>> Ronaldo is one of your role models.
>> Yeah.
>> Can you tell me what some advice you
received from him? I It's a friend now.
It's It's so great to have people that
you idolize when you're young and they
become your friends. We We used to talk
a lot together. He helped me a lot when
I was in Madrid in my first year because
he know Madrid really well. He's been
like almost 10 years in Madrid. So, we
have a wonderful good relationship and
I'm happy with that. And of course, I
was happy to talk with him the first
time because he was someone that I
idolized when I was young.
Uh but I'm not someone who's scared or
shy, so it's easy for me. Kylian, if
football didn't exist Okay. what do you
think you'd be doing right now? I think
I would working with kids to help kids
because I always say that I love kids
and they are the future of the world.
So, I will try to to give them the best
tips in life to to have the best life
possible. In 2018, you were a teenager
playing in your first World Cup. In
2022, you were a breakout star. What
does 2026 have in store? I captain now.
I'm the captain of the team. It's
different now. It's a different
responsibility. But I'm ready for that.
I'm ready to lead my team
to the biggest stage again. And And I
hope that we going to go back with the
trophy in Paris and in the
Champs-Élysées.
I think when you play, you don't think
about the legacy. You think about
to perform and to to bring the trophy
home. But of course, if we win and if I
win, it's going to be insane for the
legacy of the country and my legacy for
sure. Guys, we had a nice time, but I
got to go. So, thank you for everything
and see you soon.
Thank you to come.
>> That's a cut.